{
    "subject": "Kenneth_Branagh",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Henry_V__1989_film_",
    "human_readable": "Kenneth Branagh acted in the film Henry V (1989).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878438711166382,
            "question": "What role did Kenneth Branagh play in Henry V (1989)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9840304851531982,
            "question": "Was Kenneth Branagh involved in the making of Henry V (1989)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9766627550125122,
            "question": "Has Kenneth Branagh acted in other films besides Henry V (1989)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9550716280937195,
            "question": "Who acted in the film Henry V (1989)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7756778597831726,
            "question": "What is the title of the film starring Kenneth Branagh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7436075806617737,
            "question": "In what film did Kenneth Branagh act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7054991126060486,
            "question": "Is Kenneth Branagh a known actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6961845755577087,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Kenneth Branagh."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.590461015701294,
            "question": "What genre is the film Henry V (1989) likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47587379813194275,
            "question": "What year was the film Henry V released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kenneth Branagh acted in the film Henry V (1989).",
            "html": "yago_21966_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Henry V (1989) likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_21966_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Kenneth Branagh.",
            "html": "yago_21966_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kenneth Branagh a known actor?",
            "html": "yago_21966_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21966_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Kenneth Branagh directing and starring in the 1989 film adaptation of William Shakespeare's play \"Henry V\". This information supports the statement that Kenneth Branagh acted in the film Henry V (1989)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several pieces of information that support this triple. Specifically, it mentions that Kenneth Branagh stars in the title role and acts alongside other actors in the 1989 film \"Henry V,\" directed by himself. This clearly indicates his involvement as an actor in the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}